I just had a birthday and
yeah,
and I know it's hard to tell how old I
am cuz I'm half black and Asian.
You know what they say, black don't
crack. Asian no raisin.
I'm 137 years old.
I know, man. You're looking at me. It's
tough. It's tough being blazing. It's
hard in these streets.
It's hard in these streets of Provo,
man.
Cuz people don't know what I am. You
know, I go to Miami right now. I'm
Puerto Rican.
I went to New York. I was Dominican.
I went to Hawaii. They were like,
"Welcome home."
I love it though, man. I love it cuz cuz
I love my parents and that's who I am.
Black and Asian. Like my dad is black,
just turned 80 years old, you know.
Yeah, that's right. It's awesome.
Has a PhD in nuclear physics and served
our country in the army. That's my dad
right there.
Now, I love them. And here's the thing
about black men, you need to know. They
got swag. When they young, they got
swag. When they old, they got swag. My
dad's 80 years old and he walks around
the house like this. You know what I
mean?
And he's always laughing. He like
And he's always pointing at things that
aren't even there. LIKE
my mom, she was born and raised in
Korea, Southside.
Now we know who doesn't watch the news
in this world.
Tough having an Asian mom is tough, man.
If they think it, they say it. They
don't care about feelings. That's the
thing about Asian moms. They don't care
about feelings. My mom, oh, she'll say
whatever's on her mind all the time. She
won't even say people's names anymore.
She knows your name, but she won't say
it. She would rather describe you.
She called me up the other day and goes,
"I met your friend." I go, "Which one?"
She goes, "Fat boy, small feet."
But I knew exactly who she was talking
about.
Cuz the thing about my mom, she will say
the rudest thing to your face and not
care. Cuz she believes she can say
anything to anybody. Cuz it's a true. Is
it true?
Oh, you don't like true?
Why you mad? Is it true?
Do I lie?
My mom got in a fight with my wife. Now,
full disclosure, my wife, she cooks like
once every couple, you know, like once.
So, my mom walks into our new house and
goes, "Oh, what a beautiful kitchen
for no cooking."
I go, "Mom, you can't say that to my
wife. Not in my house." She goes, "Why?
Is it true? Is it true?"
Then she looks at me and my wife and
goes, "Do I lie?"
I look at my dad for help. My dad's
like, "Walk away, son. Walk away."
>> My parents been married for 52 years.
They just celebrated 52 years in
marriage.
Beautiful, beautiful, beautiful.
I asked my dad. I just celebrated 10
years. And I asked my dad, I said, "How
do you stay married so long?" My dad
looks me straight in the face and goes,
"That's simple, son. Never say the first
or second thing that pops into your
head.
Always say the third." I go, "What does
that mean?" He goes, "Well, if you say
the first thing, you will get a divorce.
Second thing, you might not be in the
house, but the third thing, son, happily
ever after."
I never understood it. I never
understood it till about 6 months ago.
Me and my wife are driving from LA to
Las Vegas. She packs a cooler of food
for our daughter. We get to Las Vegas.
My wife opens up the cooler and goes,
"Oh my gosh, the food all melted." I
look in the cooler and notice she didn't
put any ice in it.
You
But I'm a man. I'm a man. We have this
voice in our head, right, man? My voice
in my head was like, "YOU NEED TO LET
HER KNOW she need to put ice in the
cooler." Now, I don't know why the voice
in my head sounds like a 70s pimp, but
it does.
>> I don't know. I don't know why.
So I look at my wife. I go, "Baby, baby,
it melted
cuz
you didn't put ice in the cooler." My
wife looks at me dead in the eye and
goes, "You don't need to put ice in a
cooler. It's a cooler. Duh."
Now, the first thing I thought was,
"That's the dumbest thing I EVER HEARD
IN MY LIFE.
BUT I DIDN'T SAY THE FIRST THING. I
didn't say the second thing. I said the
third thing. I go, "Baby, I can't
believe this cooler
is broken."
Now, if you don't know anything about my
family, my wife, we celebrated 10 years
of marriage. She white, but she not just
white. She white. White.
Yeah, she's organic uh freerange white.
She's farmers market white.
My wife is so white if she got caught
shoplifting they would help her carry
the bags.
My wife is from Gillette, Wyoming
whites.
>> A lot of white people in HERE WERE LIKE
WHOA.
You know when white people in Provo are
like, "WHOA."
I went to Gillette, Wyoming, they were
so confused. They were like, "I didn't
know Lionel Richie did comedy.
Shut up.
After being married for 10 years, I
learned a lot about you women in here. I
know a lot about you women. And I will
say this, and this is to every single
woman in this room from the bottom of my
heart. I think you are amazing. I think
women are amazing.
I want you to notice only about 20% of
the women clapped cuz the other women in
this room were like, "But what you going
to say next?"
I'mma double down on it. I think women
make men great. I think a good woman
makes a man great. But you got to
understand there's a lot of guys that
don't agree with that. You know, I was
in this place called Alabama.
A guy comes up to me after the show
goes, "Hey, I just want to let you know
I make my wife great." I was like,
"Okay,
how you do that?" He goes, "I give her
emotional support." I go, "No, you
don't. She got a group text for that.
Right, ladies? All the ladies know all
day long. All day long, fellas. Your
ladies on the phone with their best
girlfriends getting emotional support
just back and forth. I've never seen so
many prayer hands in my life. That's all
I do.
Fire, fire,
fire, fire.
My wife right now could text her best
girlfriends. I feel ugly. Send it off.
One minute later, every single
girlfriend has replied, "No, you're not.
You a queen. Shine bright like a
diamond."
Fellas, we don't support each other like
that. No, we don't. I can't text my guy
friends, I feel ugly.
They'll be like, YOU ARE REALLY UGLY.
A guy after my last show, a guy after my
last show ran up to me with a cell
phone. He goes, "Look, yo, I did it. I
did it." He texts his best friend, "I
feel ugly." His friend wrote back, "DIE.
Let's go.